The Perfect Catch is a romance, drama, tv movie
film directed by Steven R. Monroe.
When Jessica Parker’s former high school boyfriend, superstar baseball player Chase Taynor, returns to town, she finds the
inspiration to reinvent her struggling diner… and revisits the past to find something even better for the future.
Jessica Parker, played by Nikki DeLoach.
Chase Taynor, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Nina, played by Lisa Durupt.
Wesley, played by Chance Hurstfield.
Brett Thompson, played by Vincent Dangerfield.
Lindy Taynor, played by P. Lynn Johnson.
Perfect Stranger is a 2007 American psychological thriller film, directed
by James Foley, and starring Halle Berry and Bruce Willis.
It was produced by Revolution Studios for Columbia
Pictures, who released the film on April 13, 2007.
The film was panned by critics, with its twist ending being the most criticized, and
underperformed at the box office, grossing $73.5 million on a $60 million budget.
The film explores themes of sports, baseball player,
high school sweetheart, hallmark.
The tone is emotional.